this happened on bbc.com Google is
trying to make our Emoji more diverse no
they aren't adding a diarrhea Emoji
although they should although what would
it be would it be just like one Splat
with eyes would it be would the eyes be
like me would it like stretch across an
entire line of text would there be an
explosion point would there be a
splatter Point what would it be anyway
they want to make new Emoji for
professional women and is about goddamn
time
because Jes the only ones currently will
feature women in stereotypical roles
like wife and salsa dancer stomping a
bug so Google Engineers designed 13
Emoji of professional women and
presented them for approval to the
governing body of emoji the Unicode
Consortium which sounds a lot like the
name of a store set in the World of
Harry
Potter here's some they're proposing uh
sweet awesome Healthcare professionals
that's a no-brainer uh what else we got
yes absolutely scientist duh of course
absolutely uh women have made tons of
amazing contri R butions to science is
absolutely deserved what else oh a
welder all right sure why not listen hey
come
on but uh while I do believe that uh
there are absolutely women welders I
don't know when you would ever use this
Emoji I can't quite come up with a
circumstance where a lady welder Emoji
would might a to help you with that I
wonder if there were only some comedians
here who might be able to send a text
that would require a female welding
Emoji uh Randy scare hey guys just
putting the finishing touches on that
glass ceiling those guys had me build
hey nice very good uh Jason scar uh Mom
and Dad I'm a lesbian a flaming
lesbian John door um it's uh Happy
Father's Day I
uh ran out of money but I thought you
could jerk off to this Jesus
Christ no reason why we can't jerk off
to women in the workplace it's my fault
it's all my
fault